[music]
yours
>> pretty good. We got some guys that'll
work through the week, you know, with um
anyway, I think all the guys that are
kind of listed the other day, we'll work
through the week and see where they end
up.
>> So, I gonna practice today?
>> No. Okay.
>> What's the likelihood that he's able to
go this week?
>> Um I'm not going to roll him out today.
back have a lot of mouths to feed on
offense. Um I think Chase Brown's
averaging like 17 and some change
touches a game. Is there a sweet spot
for him you think touch-wise or is it
just
>> just varies because it varies?
>> It varies because it varies. It varies
because how the team's playing us, you
know, so whatever personnel we got on
the field. Um he gets really good
matchups.
So there's a lot of times we we make him
one the progression um because if he
gets the matchup, take it. And there's
times where it's the coverage or the the
coverage didn't dictate it and we move
on quickly. But um I don't look at it as
how many carries a game did he get.
We're just I think pitch does a really
good job of driving like let's make sure
we got x amount of ways that can get all
of our playmakers the ball. Um doesn't
mean it's going to happen that way
during the game, but making sure that we
have opportunities for all those guys.
>> How much has he expanded his route tree
from [clears throat] training camp to
this year even
>> rookie training camp? said
>> expanded certainly. You know, it's you
don't always get the opportunity to use
it a million different ways, but
>> just flexing out and running the route.
We ran the other day for the touchdown's
good. He does that out of the back field
a lot where he's got the choice to go
three different directions that way. Um
that one's more of a a prescribed
outbreaker. Uh but we've had him on a
lot of things. Again, it the coverage
doesn't always take us there, but we
have a lot of trust that he can he can
run a lot of different routes and be a
good matchup for us. Have you enjoyed
seeing the change up of uh two running
backs on the field at the same time and
what that's done for you guys?
>> Yeah, we're trying to find as many ways
to again uh that has a lot to do with
our confidence as Sama and different
ways to use Chase and put him in space.
Try to try to make people have to cover
us a lot of different ways.
>> What makes Sama so effective when he's
been in the game and y'all called his
number?
>> He's really physical. Uh really smart
runner. So he knows where the creases
are and how to get that extra two,
three, four yards.
Um, tremendous in protection obviously.
Uh, has a great knack and feel for Joe
in the passing game, you know,
particularly on checkdowns and and
things like that of understanding where
to be and when. [clears throat] So just
as an allound player, um, he brings
significant value to our team.
>> When you look at Arizona, what they what
they do well, what kind of jumps out on
the table? they, you know, they're going
to try to stretch you some different
ways on defense. That's unique
[clears throat] from some teams you play
against. Um, so that takes time during a
week to to be ready for some of the
presentations they're going to give you,
different personnel groupings, different
coverage structures. They like to
utilize Buddha Baker a lot of different
ways and get him activated. And um, you
know, offensively, I think Trey McBride
is is a phenomenal tight end. You know,
they they use him really um, all the
ways we try to get Jamar the ball. You
know, you see that from Trey, he's not
going to line up outside the numbers
necessarily and run the full route tree
out there, but um they'll put him out
there and kind of the way you see used
in Philly a little bit to try to get
some matchups and um his Colorado State
tape was full of these middle screens.
I'd never really seen a tight end catch
before and lo and behold, they're
they're using them like crazy on that.
So, um they're just trying to find a way
to get him the ball every which way
imaginable. They do a great job of it,
covered or uncovered. He's got really
strong hands. Um he's a really physical
runner, violent runner. Um, one one of a
really impressive impressive players in
this league.
>> I was gonna ask you, what did you make
of his pre-draft eval? What you
[clears throat] guys
>> loved him. Yeah, I loved him. Um, yeah,
we loved him.
>> Jamar's deep ball against Miami. Looked
a lot like the Kansas City playoff deep
ball. Um, kind of a double double.
>> Yeah.
>> Um, how important is it when teams throw
double double at you guys to kind of now
and then beat it anyway with Jamar? you
have to because you can't just let a
team take away your star players and um
so I I mean our coaching staff has put a
lot of work into that you know whether
it's pitch Troy or Scotty Brad all the
different areas that we hone in on to
defeat the coverage structures they're
going to give us and um sometimes that's
just Joe making an adjustment and Jamar
being on the same page and Joe with a
subtle subtle you know audible at the
last second hand signal a lot of times
things we've discussed a lot of times
Joe's got a great awareness what the
coverage is going to be and he and Joe
Jamar are in tune with it. Uh T's the
same way. We see the same stuff from T.
So T's always ready for it as well. Um
but then to go make that play on a third
down, that was that was a big play for
us.
>> The concussions on T, have you all
adjusted the practice schedule for him
at all? How does that is there anything
different out of protocol now that y'all
do anything with him?
>> No, I mean we we don't I mean in theory
we're not contacting practice,
especially with our receivers, so it it
doesn't really change anything. talked a
little about Jaylen Davis the other day
and if you look at his transaction
history it's lengthy of waves signed
signed to a practice squad [snorts]
what's his perseverance
>> I mean same guy everything you wanted a
guy to be that we've preached in our
locker room same guy every day you know
when he walks in the building what
you're going to get from JD you're going
to get tremendous energy good vibes guy
uh great sense of humor person that
everybody likes being around he's going
to work he's got a knack for making
plays great communicator
really high football IQ
Um, you know, so just all the things you
would you'd drop in a player and I'm
sure it's frustrating for him. You know,
I've had a lot of training camp final
cut days, you know, where, hey JD, here
we are again, you know, and uh, we know
we can count on you on the practice
squad and if there's an elevation, we
know we can get you up here and do it.
And and so for him just to make the most
of the opportunity, you're you're just
you're really happy for him to get that
opportunity. Um, because he deserves it.
He's worked hard for it. just a great
human, great player. Uh, one of those
glue guys in the locker room that you
got to have because um he just he makes
everybody around you happier, better um
just really really happy for him.
>> Have teams ever take him off the
practice? How does that happen?
>> Um probably better off staying away from
that. I don't even know what my answer
is, but
>> back to house.
>> Thank you.
>> [music]